Marvelous Designer is a professional 3D costume design software
which is widely used in games, animation, and visual effects.
This year, the Academy of Fine Arts and Science,
which is the sponsor of the Oscar Gold Medal,
has been awarded the Marvelous Designer Team's
Technology and Science Achievement Award.
Clover Virtual Fashion and Epic Games
have been partners for many years,
but this is our first offline collaboration in China.
This year, we have launched two new features,
the SYNC plug-in and the USB-C module data.
We hope to share these two features with you
through this presentation
to help you improve your work efficiency.
The main purpose of our participation in this exhibition
is to let the users of Marvelous Designer in China know
that we, Marvelous Designer,
have a very strong team in China
that can always support you.
We hope that you can pay more attention
to our official accounts and Bilibili.
We will continue to update you with new features
and different kinds of information.
This is our gaming studio in Shanghai.
We have been using the MD11 and 12 versions for a while.
Through today's presentation,
we learned that MD2024 has a lot of new features,
including the combination of Unreal Engine.
We hope that in the future,
we can have more technology exchanges
to make this product and our game better.
Thank you for watching.